octoly.com 2016-04-04

# Octoly.com

Protecting your private information is Octoly's priority. This Statement of Privacy governs the use of Octoly.com ("Website") and the services related to or offered on the Website (hereinafter, the "Services"), and governs data collection and usage by Octoly, Inc. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to "Octoly" will include Octoly.com, Octoly, Inc. and its affiliates. The Octoly website is a business networking and ecommerce site. By using the Website or Services, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

Octoly may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address ("Personal Information"). If you purchase Octoly's products and Services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. Octoly may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income and race. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. Your Personal Information will be processed by Octoly in and/or outside of the United States.

If you access or log-in to the Website and/or Services through a social media or other service or connect the Website and/or Services to a social media or other service, the information Octoly collects may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content you have permitted the social media service to share with Octoly, such as your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the Website and/or Services through social media services or when you connect the Website and/or Service to social media services, you are authorizing Octoly to collect, store, and use such information and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Octoly. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Octoly website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Octoly's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Octoly encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Octoly so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Octoly is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Octoly website.

## Use of your Personal Information

Octoly collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the Services you have requested.

Octoly may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Octoly and its affiliates. Octoly may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Octoly does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Octoly may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party, including without limitation certain information received from your social media platform login. Octoly may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Octoly, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Octoly may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Octoly, in order to determine what Octoly services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Octoly to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Octoly will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Octoly or the Website; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Octoly; (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Octoly, or the public and (d) as necessary to perform the Services requested by you.

## Use of Cookies/Targeted Advertising

The Octoly website may use tracking technology such as "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Octoly pages, or register with the Octoly Website or Services, a cookie helps Octoly to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Octoly website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Octoly features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Octoly services or websites you visit.

Octoly may also use cookies, pixels, web beacons (which are usually small, transparent graphic images), operating system and device information and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit, the features and information for which you searched and viewed, the email you opened, or on which advertisements you clicked.

Octoly works with third party companies (e.g., ad networks) that may use cookies for purposes including, without limitation, understanding Web usage patterns of users who see advertisements on the Website, controlling the sequence of advertisements you see, making sure you don't see the same advertisement too many times, determining your interests and tailoring advertisements and promotions based on those interests. The advertisement may appear when you are visiting a different section of this Website, another Website or any other website on the Internet if the website also has a relationship with Octoly's vendor. You can choose to limit Behavioral Advertising on the Website by clicking http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ and opting-out of cookies placed by those vendors listed. After you opt-out, you will still see advertisements but the advertising may not be as relevant to your interests. If you change your computer, change your browser, or delete your cookies, you will need to renew your opt-out.

Octoly adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising of the Digital Advertising Alliance (for more information click here at http://www.aboutads.info/consumers).

Advertisers or other third parties on the Website may also engage in Behavioral Advertising and use cookies and web beacons in the manner described above. Octoly does not control these advertisers or other parties' use of cookies or web beacons or what they do with the information they collect. Many third party vendors that engage in Behavioral Advertising participate in the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and/or the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) and abide by NAI and/or DAA principles. If you wish to opt out of participating in advertising programs conducted by NAI and DAA members or learn more about the NAI and DAA, please go to the NAI OPT-OUT website (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and DAA CHOICE PAGE (http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) and follow the instructions. After you opt-out, you will still see advertisements, but the advertising may not be as relevant to your interests. If you change your computer, change your browser or delete your cookies, you will need to renew your opt-out.

## Security of your Personal Information

Octoly secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. Octoly does not warrant the security of its servers, nor does Octoly warrant that your information, including Personal Information, will be completely secure or not be intercepted while being transmitted over the Internet.

## Children Under Thirteen

Octoly does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

## Disconnecting your Octoly Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your Octoly account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR OCTOLY ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their "My Account" page. Users may also contact us via email or telephone.

## Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an product to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Octoly by by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive or contacting us here:

\- Web page: https://www.octoly.com/#contact

\- Email: success@octoly.com

\- Phone: 646-844-9398

At this time Octoly does not respond to browser 'Do Not Track' signals, as Octoly awaits the work of interested stakeholders and others to develop standards for how such signals should be interpreted.

## Other Information

The Website may link to websites operated by third parties that Octoly does not control. Octoly does not monitor, control, or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any third parties. Octoly encourages you to become familiar with the privacy practices of every website you visit and to contact them if you have any questions about their respective privacy policies and practices. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Octoly through the Website or Services and does not apply to these third party websites. The ability to access information of third parties from the Website or Services, or links to other websites or locations, is for your convenience only and does not signify Octoly's endorsement of such third parties, their products, services, websites, locations or their content.

In addition, Octoly is not responsible for the privacy or data security practices of other organizations, such as YouTube, Facebook, Tumblr, Twitter, Apple, Google, Microsoft or any other app developer, app provider, social media platform provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider, or device manufacturer, including in connection with any information you disclose to other organizations through or in connection with the Services.

Octoly will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Octoly encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Octoly is protecting your information.

## Contact Information

Octoly welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Octoly has not adhered to this statement, please contact Octoly at: 

Octoly, Inc.

244 Fifth Avenue, Suite D61 New York, N.Y. 10001 

Email Address:

success@octoly.com

Telephone number:

646-844-9398 

Effective as of October 13, 2015
